A Guide to the University of Virginia Facilities Management Architectural and Engineering Services Project Photographs and Slides
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Facilities Management
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-31/1/3.061
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
The papers were an archival transfer from the Facilities Management Resource Center, 2006 August.
Scope and Content
The collection contains photographs and slides of Facilities Management projects, 1982-1992, in-process and completed for both new construction and renovations. Images Projects range from ramps, lights and sidewalks to building additions and the Klockner Stadium.
In addition there are images from a staff picnic in 1988, preparations for the President's Education Summit with state governors in 1989. Many of these were taken by Michael Bailey or Clay S. Palazzo. Several, depicting physical plant staff at their jobs, may have been taken for William D. Middleton's APPA presentation in July, 1983.
Additional images, 1985-1992, were used by Middleton in presentations to various groups including the Board of Visitors. Many of these are of site plans, charts, models, renderings and other preliminary items. There are also photograph negatives of Physical Plant publications.
Contents List
- Series I: University Photographs (1983-1998)
  - 1993 Aug Award for Excellence in Facilities Management, 6 items (Box-folder 1:1)
  - 1983-1992 Building Designs, 12 items (Box-folder 1:2)
  - 1983-1992 Buildings, miscellaneous, 22 items (Box-folder 1:3)
  - 1996 Apr 16 Construction by the Engineering School, 25 items (Box-folder 1:4)
  - 1983-1992 Construction Projects, miscellaneous, 18 items (Box-folder 1:5)
  - 1997 Nov-1998 Jan Drain Project, 53 items (Box-folder 1:6)
  - 1992 Feb Fan Installation of the Aquatic Fitness Center, 30 items (Box-folder 1:7)
  - 1996 Nov 13 Fire Pit, 10 items (Box-folder 1:8)
  - 1997 Dec 23 Parking Lot Work, 11 items (Box-folder 1:9)
  - 1996 Jul 2 Pipes behind Minor and Maury Halls, 15 items (Box-folder 1:10)
  - 1998 Aug 24 Pipes by the Lawn, 4 items (Box-folder 1:11)
  - 1997 Sep- Nov Pipes for a Drain, 19 items (Box-folder 1:12)
  - 1996 Mar 18 Pipes for Water Supply to Gilmer Hall, 21 items (Box-folder 1:13)
  - 1997 Jul-Sep Sidewalk Project, 20 items (Box-folder 1:14)
  - 1997 Apr Tennis Courts, 20 items (Box-folder 1:15)
- Series II: University Slides (1983-1992)
  - 1993 Jan 28 Index for Notebooks 1-3, 1 items (Box-folder 1:16)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook 1 (folder 1 of 3), 183 items (Box-folder 1:17)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook 1 (folder 2 of 3), 142 items (Box-folder 1:18)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook 1 (folder 3 of 3), 97 items (Box-folder 1:19)
  - 1982-1992 Notebook 2 (folder 1 of 3), 138 items (Box-folder 2:1)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook 2 (folder 2 of 3), 159 items (Box-folder 2:2)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook 2 (folder 3 of 3), 181 items (Box-folder 2:3)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook 3 (folder 1 of 2), 141 items (Box-folder 2:4)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook 3 (folder 2 of 2), 75 items (Box-folder 2:5)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook on the Physical Plant (folder 1 of 3), 134 items (Box-folder 2:6)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook on the Physical Plant (folder 2 of 3), 166 items (Box-folder 2:7)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook on the Physical Plant (folder 3 of 3), 163 items (Box-folder 3:1)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook on Presentations (folder 1 of 2), 104 items (Box-folder 3:2)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook on Presentations (folder 2 of 2), 105 items (Box-folder 3:3)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook on Project Slides, 116 items (Box-folder 3:4)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook on Various Building Projects (folder 1 of 3), 169 items (Box-folder 3:5)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook on Various Building Projects (folder 2 of 3), 137 items (Box-folder 3:6)
  - 1983-1992 Notebook on Various Building Projects (folder 3 of 3), 106 items (Box-folder 3:7)
  - 1983-1992 Structures at the University of Virginia (folder 1 of 2), 124 items (Box-folder 3:8)
  - 1983-1992 Structures at the University of Virginia (folder 2 of 2), 80 items (Box-folder 3:9)